Register of the Survey of Race Relations records
Hoover Institution Archives
- Minor Documents, 1907-1934 (Boxes 33-38)
  - Life history of Lui Wing as a social document (Box-folder 35: 206)
    11 pages; Life histories, Chinese customs, Tongs, Communities; Chinese; Seattle) – Missing
  - Life history of F. H. Marr as a social document (Box-folder 35: 207)
    6 pages; Life histories, Race consciousness, Competition and land: Business, Tongs, Social disorganization: Gambling, Exclusion; Chinese; Seattle) - Missing
  - Life history of Loui Youu as social document (Box-folder 35: 208)
    4 pages; Life histories, Population: Immigration, Americanization: Accommodation; Chinese; Seattle) – Missing
  - Interview with Tsuruyo Komoriya (Box-folder 35: 209)
    4 pages; Life histories, Americanization: Accommodation, Race consciousness, Goodwill; Japanese; Seattle) - Missing
  - Life history and social document of Yong Chin (Box-folder 35: 210)
    4 pages; Life histories, Race consciousness, Americanization; Chinese; Seattle) – Missing
  - Life history of Chin Sing as social document (Box-folder 35: 211)
    6 pages; Life histories, Population: Immigration, Investigations: Legislation, Tongs, Race consciousness; Chinese; Seattle) - Missing
  - Interview of C. W. Bagley as social document (Box-folder 35: 212)
    6 pages; Investigations: Historical, Racial traits; Chinese; Seattle) - Missing
  - Interview of C. H. Hanford, Judge, as social document (Box-folder 35: 213)
    3 pages; Investigations: Historical, Social disorganization; Chinese; Seattle) - Missing
  - Life history of Kay Yen Wu as social document (Box-folder 35: 214)
    6 pages; Life histories, Americanization: Education and Second generation, Tongs, Population: Immigration; Chinese; Seattle) - Missing
  - Fairfax, Washington, Lumber Camp (Box-folder 35: 215)
    2 pages; Competition and land, Other: Industry, Communities; Japanese; Portland) - Missing
  - Interview with Manley Moore Lumber Company foreman, and other employees (Box-folder 35: 216)
    14 pages; Competition and land: Labor; Japanese; Seattle) - Missing
  - Life histories of three employees, Manley Moore Lumber Company (Box-folder 35: 217)
    7 pages; Life histories; Japanese; Seattle) - Missing
  - Interview with T. H. Soo, China Trading Company, Seattle (Box-folder 35: 218)
    12 pages; Life histories, Americanization: Vocational problems, Competition and land: Business; Chinese; Seattle) - Missing
  - Interview with Andrew Kan, China Trading Company (Box-folder 35: 219)
    6 pages; Life histories, Population: Immigration, Tongs, Americanization: Family problems, Social disorganization: Gambling; Chinese; Seattle) - Missing
  - Life history and social document of Woo Bing, Seattle (Box-folder 35: 220)
    6 pages; Life histories; Chinese; Seattle) – Missing
  - General information from employees, Wheeler Osgood Company, Tacoma (Box-folder 35: 221)
    5 pages; Competition and land: Labor, Life histories; Japanese; Seattle) - Missing
  - General information regarding employees, Tide Water Mill Company (Box-folder 35: 222)
    5 pages; Competition and land: Labor; Japanese; Seattle) – Missing
  - General information regarding employees, Defiance Lumber Company (Box-folder 35: 223)
    1 page; Competition and land; Japanese; Seattle) - Missing
  - General information regarding North End Lumber Company (Box-folder 35: 224)
    1 page; Competition and land: Labor; Japanese; Seattle) - Missing
  - General information regarding Foster-Nebegin Lumber Company (Box-folder 35: 225)
    2 pages; Competition and land: Labor, Communities; Japanese; Seattle) – Missing
  - (a) General information regarding McMillin Lumber Company (Box-folder 35: 226)
    5 pages; Competition and land: Labor, Race; Japanese; Seattle) - Missing
    - (b) Interview with Y. Hamaguchi, Japanese foreman
  - Interview with T. Matsushita of McMillin Lumber Company (Box-folder 35: 227)
  - General information regarding Nettleton Lumber Company employees (Box-folder 35: 228)
    3 pages; Competition and land: Labor, Racial traits; Japanese; Seattle) - Missing
  - Interview with S. Kawamura, Nettleton Lumber Company (Box-folder 35: 229)
    3 pages; Life histories; Japanese; Seattle) - Missing
  - Various interviews with men connected with Snoqualmie Falls Lumber Company (Box-folder 35: 230)
    28 pages; Competition and land: Labor, Life histories; Japanese; Seattle) - Missing
  - General information and interviews with men employed by Pacific States Lumber Company, Selleck, Washington (Box-folder 35: 231)
    20 pages; Competition and land: Labor, Life histories; Japanese; Seattle) - Missing
  - Interviews and general information regarding men employed by White River Lumber Company (Box-folder 35: 232)
    10 pages; Competition and land: Labor, Life histories; Japanese; Seattle) - Missing
  - General information and interview with K. Otani, Japanese foreman, J. P. Guerrier Lumber Company, Forest, Washington (Box-folder 35: 233)
    2 pages; Competition and land: Labor, Life histories; Japanese; Seattle) - Missing
  - General information regarding McCormick Lumber Company, McCormick, Washington (Box-folder 35: 234)
    2 pages; Life histories, Competition and land: labor; Japanese; Seattle) - Missing
  - Interview with I. Mori, Japanese foreman, McCormick Lumber Company (Box-folder 35: 235)
    1 page; Life histories; Japanese; Seattle) - Missing
  - General information and interviews with Japanese employed by Green River Lumber Company, McIntosh, Washington (Box-folder 35: 236)
    3 pages; Competition and land: Labor, Racial traits; Japanese; Seattle) – Missing
  - General information regarding Japanese employees, Dea Chutes Lumber Company (Box-folder 35: 237)
    1 page; Competition and land: labor; Japanese; Seattle) - Missing
  - General information regarding Japanese employees, Lindstrom-Handforth Lumber Company, Rainer, Washington (Box-folder 35: 238)
    3 pages; Competition and land: Labor, Life histories; Japanese; Seattle) – Missing
  - General information regarding A. J. West Lumber Company, Junction City, Washington (Box-folder 35: 239)
  - General information regarding employment of Japanese labor by Schafer Brothers Lumber and Door Company, Montesamo, Washington (Box-folder 35: 240)
    2 pages; Competition and land: labor; Japanese; Seattle) – Missing
  - Interviews on Japanese question, Fresno, California (Box-folder 35: 241)
    1 page; Racial traits, Americanization: Accommodation; Japanese; Northern California) - Missing
  - Interviews regarding Japanese question, Fresno, California (Box-folder 35: 242)
    8 pages; Americanization: Accommodation, Racial traits, Competition and land: Agriculture, Communities; Japanese; Northern California) – Missing
  - Report, race relations on the Japanese, Fresno, California (Box-folder 35: 243)
    3 pages; Communities, Americanization, Investigations; Japanese; Northern California) - Missing
  - Report, Americans, Fresno, California (Box-folder 35: 244)
    6 pages; Communities, Investigations: Historical, Racial traits; American; Northern California) - Missing
  - Report, interviews concerning American labor, Fresno (Box-folder 35: 245)
    6 pages; Racial traits, Competition and land: Agriculture, Race consciousness; American; Northern California) - Missing
  - Interviews with Armenian Pastor, Fresno, California (Box-folder 35: 246)
    2 pages; Americanization, Intermarriage; American; Northern California) - Missing
  - Interview with Americanization teacher, Fresno Public Schools (Box-folder 35: 247)
    2 pages; Americanization; Japanese; Northern California) - Missing
  - Opinion of Director, Farm Bureau, Fresno, on the Japanese and other races (Box-folder 35: 248)
    7 pages; Competition and land: Agriculture and labor, Racial traits; Japanese; Northern California) - Missing
  - Report, East Indians, Fresno (Box-folder 35: 249)
    3 pages; Communities, Competition and land: Labor, Racial traits; Hindu; Northern California) - Missing
  - "A Chinese Marriage," San Francisco Journal, 1922 January 22 (Box-folder 35: 250)
    1 page; Intermarriage; Chinese; Northern California
  - "Japanese Matron Prefers America," San Francisco Chronicle, 1922 March 3 (Box-folder 35: 251)
    1 page; Intermarriage; Japanese; Northern California
  - "East and West Sometimes Do Meet: As Marriage of Occident and Orient Shows," San Francisco Call, 1923 December 20 (Box-folder 35: 252)
  - "The Woman Without a Country," Boston Transcript (Box-folder 35: 253)
    3 pages; Intermarriage, Investigations: Legislation; Northern California
  - "Briton and Japanese Wife are Visiting San Francisco, Come from Manchuria on Pleasure Trip: Celebrate Wedding Anniversary with an Extended Tour," San Francisco Chronicle, 1923 May 22 (Box-folder 35: 254)
  - "Why Japanese and Americans Should not Inter-Marry," San Francisco Bulletin, 1922 June 15 (Box-folder 35: 255)
  - "Survey, Hood River, Oregon," by Helen W. Howe, Pendleton, Oregon (Box-folder 35: 256)
    4 pages; Competition and land: Agriculture; Japanese; Portland
  - Interview with Ishi, Secretary, Japanese Association, El Centro, California (Box-folder 35: 257)
    2 pages; Competition and land: Agriculture, Intermarriage; Japanese; Southern California) – Missing
  - Interview with George Maga, Japanese, Y. M. (Box-folder 35: 258)
    1 page; Americanization; Japanese; Southern California) – Missing
  - Interview with E. C. Paris, El Centro, California (Box-folder 35: 259)
    1 page; Competition and land: Agriculture; Hindu and Japanese; Southern California) - Missing
  - The Japanese and life insurance (Box-folder 35: 260)
    1 page; Americanization: Accommodation; Japanese and Mexican; Southern California) - Missing
  - "Life of Senora Ramona Diaz," as told by herself (Box-folder 35: 261)
    4 pages; Life histories; Mexican; Southern California
  - "Life History of Senora Angelita Avila," as told by herself (Box-folder 35: 262)
    7 pages; Life histories; Mexican; Southern California
  - Life history of Francisco Carino (Box-folder 35: 263)
    20 pages; Life histories; Filipino; Southern California) - Missing
  - Unpleasant experience of Japanese renting a house in Seattle (Box-folder 35: 264)
    5 pages; Race consciousness; Japanese; Seattle
  - "Interview with Arthur C. Ballard," Auburn, Washington, by Van Devanter, 1924 July 7 (Box-folder 35: 265)
    1 pages; Competition and land: Agriculture; Japanese; Seattle
  - "Interview with Mrs. Arthur C. Ballard," Auburn, Washington, by Van Devanter, 1924 July 13 (Box-folder 35: 266)
    1 page; Americanization: Education; Japanese; Seattle
  - "Interview with Rufus R. Upper," Orillia, Washington, by Van Devanter, 1924 July 14 (Box-folder 35: 267)
    1 page; Competition and land: Agriculture, Racial traits; Chinese; Seattle
  - Interview with Aaron Neely, Auburn, Washington (Box-folder 35: 268)
    2 pages; Competition and land: Agriculture and Business; Japanese; Seattle) - Missing
  - "Interview with W. T. Behne," President, First National Bank, Auburn, Washington, by Van Devanter, 1924 July 17 (Box-folder 35: 269)
    1 page; Racial traits, Competition and land: Agriculture; Japanese; Seattle
  - "Interview with Mr. and Mrs. Elmer E. Truitt," Auburn, Washington, by Van Devanter, 1924 July 26 (Box-folder 35: 270)
    2 pages; Racial traits, Competition and land: Labor; Japanese and Chinese; Seattle
  - "Interview with Mr. and Mrs. Eathel Smith," Auburn, Washington, by Van Devanter, 1924 July 2 (Box-folder 35: 271)
    1 pages; Competition and land: Labor; Japanese and Chinese; Seattle
  - "Interview with Bernice Welch," teacher, Seattle, by Van Devanter, 1924 July 24 (Box-folder 35: 272)
    2 pages; Intermarriage, Racial traits; Japanese; Seattle
  - "Interview with C. C. Calavan," cashier, Auburn National Bank, Auburn, Washington, by Van Devanter, 1924 July 17 (Box-folder 35: 273)
    1 page; Racial traits; Japanese; Seattle
  - Interview with A. S. McDaniel, Auburn, Washington (Box-folder 35: 274)
    5 pages; Competition and land: Agriculture, Racial traits; Japanese; Seattle) - Missing
  - "Interview with W. S. Wiley," Auburn, Washington, by Van Devanter, 1924 July 26 (Box-folder 35: 275)
    1 page; Competition and land: Labor; Japanese; Seattle
  - "Interview with F. W. Shaughnessy," Auburn, Washington, by Louise Van Devanter, 1924 July 26 (Box-folder 35: 276)
    1 page; Competition and land; Japanese; Seattle
  - "Interview with C. W. Lochridge," Auburn, Washington, by Van Devanter, 1924 July 26 (Box-folder 35: 277)
    2 pages; Competition and land: Agriculture, Racial traits; Japanese; Seattle
  - "Interview with Wakaboyashi," Seattle, by D. H. Johnston, 1924 July 15 (Box-folder 35: 278)
    1 page; Social disorganization: Vice and crime; Japanese; Seattle
  - "Interview with a Chinese man," Seattle, by D. H. Johnston, 1924 July 23 (Box-folder 35: 279)
  - "Interview with Brockett," attorney, Seattle, by D. H. Johnston, 1924 July 17 (Box-folder 35: 280)
    3 pages; Social disorganization, Tongs; Chinese; Seattle
  - "Interview with John Sullivan," attorney, Seattle, by D. H. Johnston, 1924 July 24 (Box-folder 35: 281)
    2 pages; Social disorganization, Tongs; Chinese; Seattle
  - "Interview with Adam Beeler," attorney, by D. H. Johnston, 1924 July 31 (Box-folder 35: 282)
    1 page; Racial traits, Loyalty; Chinese; Seattle
  - "Interview with Huntoon," attorney, by D. H. Johnston, 1924 June 26 (Box-folder 35: 283)
    2 pages; Social disorganization, Tongs, Racial traits; Chinese; Seattle
  - "Interview with Monroe," attorney, by D. H. Johnston, 1924 July 11 (Box-folder 35: 284)
    2 pages; Social disorganization, Tongs, Moral code; Chinese; Seattle
  - "Interview with Dan Landon," by D. H. Johnston, 1924 July 10 (Box-folder 35: 285)
    1 page; Social disorganization: Prostitution, Tongs; Chinese; Seattle
  - "Interview with Olmstead," Seattle Police, by D. H. Johnston (Box-folder 35: 286)
    1 page; Social disorganization: Prostitution and Vice and crime; Chinese; Seattle
  - "Interview with Detective Kent," by D. H. Johnston (Box-folder 35: 287)
    1 page; Social disorganization: Vice and crime and Prostitution; Chinese; Seattle
  - "Interview with Lieutenant Justice," Seattle, by D. H. Johnston, 1924 July 16 (Box-folder 35: 288)
    2 pages; Social disorganization, Racial traits; Chinese; Seattle
  - Interview with Williamson, federal narcotics agent (Box-folder 35: 289)
    1 pages; Social disorganization, Narcotics; Chinese, Japanese; Seattle
  - "Interview with Patterson," federal narcotics agent, by D. H. Johnston, 1924 July 31 (Box-folder 35: 290)
    1 page; Social disorganization, Narcotics; Chinese; Seattle
  - Miscellany, by D. H. Johnston (Box-folder 35: 291)
  - "Interview with Walter Metzenbaum," attorney, Seattle, by D. H. Johnston, 1924 August 31 (Box-folder 35: 292)
    2 pages; Racial traits, Americanization; Japanese; Seattle
  - "Interview with Fred Kato," by D. H. Johnston (Box-folder 35: 293)
  - A Chinese village in a Canadian village (Box-folder 35: 294)
    4 pages; Communities, Isolation; Chinese; Vancouver) - Missing
  - Call on editors of Chinese Times (Box-folder 35: 295)
    1 page; Communities, Press; Chinese; Vancouver) – Missing
  - Vancouver riot, 1907 September 7 (Box-folder 35: 296)
    3 pages; Race consciousness; Chinese; Vancouver) – Missing
  - Visit with Won Cumyon (Box-folder 35: 297)
    2 pages; Population: Immigration, Investigations: Historical, Competition and land: Labor; Chinese; Vancouver) - Missing
  - Interview with Chinese Consul (Box-folder 35: 298)
    2 pages; Communities, Other: Organization; Chinese; Vancouver) - Missing
  - Interview with Miss Coleman, teacher of Chinese boys (Box-folder 35: 299)
    6 pages; Communities, Americanization: Education and Second generation, Racial traits,; Chinese; Vancouver) - Missing
  - Index, report, Chinese immigration (Box-folder 35: 300)
    5 pages; Population: Immigration; Chinese; Vancouver) - Missing
  - Index, Chinese immigration (Box-folder 35: 301)
    3 pages; Population: Immigration; Chinese; Vancouver) - Missing
  - Interview with Mr. Ward, Anglican missionary (Box-folder 35: 302)
    2 pages; Population: Immigration, Social disorganization: Vice and crime; Chinese; Vancouver) - Missing
  - Visit, reading club (Box-folder 35: 303)
    2 pages; Communities, Library; Chinese; Vancouver) - Missing
  - Dinner given by the President of Chinese Benevolent Association (Box-folder 35: 304)
    3 pages; Racial traits; Chinese; Vancouver) - Missing
  - Visit, Seto More's home (Box-folder 35: 305)
    4 pages; Investigations: Historical, Communities, Art; Chinese; Vancouver) - Missing
  - Call on three Chinese associations (Box-folder 35: 306)
    5 pages; Communities, Clubs, Family, Chinese store; Chinese; Vancouver) - Missing
  - Interview with Inspector John Jackson, police force, Vancouver (Box-folder 35: 307)
    5 pages; Social disorganization: Vice and crime, Intermarriage; Chinese; Vancouver) - Missing
  - Tour through Chinatown, by Mr. Ward and Mrs. Quong (Box-folder 35: 308)
    1 page; Social disorganization: Gambling; Chinese; Vancouver) - Missing
  - Interview with McDonald, Sheriff, Vancouver (Box-folder 35: 309)
    2 pages; Racial traits, Impressions; Chinese; Vancouver) – Missing
  - Tea with Tamakia Fakuda, Japanese student, Reed College (Box-folder 35: 310)
    2 pages; Life histories, Reflections; Japanese; Portland) - Missing
  - The Japanese language schools, California, by Japanese Association (Box-folder 35: 311)
    7 pages; Communities, Americanization: Education; Japanese; Northern California) - Missing
  - Resume of California Anti-Alien Land legislation (Box-folder 35: 312)
    3 pages; Population: Immigration, Investigations: Legislation; Japanese; Northern California) – Missing
  - "Interview with Nellie Oliver," Oliver Club, Los Angeles, by William C. Smith (Box-folder 35: 313)
    1 page; Americanization, Race consciousness; Japanese, Chinese, and Mexican; Southern California
  - "Oriental Children in School," interview with Nellie Oliver, by William C. Smith (Box-folder 35: 314)
    2 pages; Americanization, Race consciousness; Japanese, Chinese, and Mexican; Southern California
  - "Interview with Mrs. ---," Hollywood, by Chloe Holt, 1924 November 8 (Box-folder 35: 315)
    2 pages; Americanization; Chinese and Japanese; Southern California
  - "Interview with Dr. Bickford," Hollywood, by Chloe Holt, 1924 November 3 (Box-folder 35: 316)
    5 pages; Social disorganization, Racial traits; Japanese; Southern California
  - "Information Regarding Quon Gay," by Chloe Holt, 1924 November 7 (Box-folder 35: 317)
    3 pages; Life histories, Goodwill; Chinese; Southern California
  - "Interview with Gibson," Hollywood, by Chloe Holt, 1924 October 28 (Box-folder 35: 318)
    2 pages; Heritages; Japanese; Southern California
  - Interview with (name withheld by request), Los Angeles, California, by Chloe Holt, 1924 October 8 (Box-folder 35: 319)
    5 pages; Communities, Race consciousness; Japanese; Southern California
  - "Business Relations with Japanese," by Samual Sogler (Box-folder 35: 320)
    3 pages; Competition and land; Japanese; Southern California
  - List of daily newspapers published in California (Box-folder 35: 321)
    4 pages; Investigations; Southern California
  - "Stories Concerning the Japanese Told by Dr. Nina Stephens," Hollywood, by Chloe Holt, 1924 November 9 (Box-folder 35: 322)
    6 pages; Social disorganization, Goodwill; Japanese; Southern California
  - "Interviews with Real Estate Dealers of Hollywood," by Chloe Holt, 1924 October 20 (Box-folder 35: 323)
    10 pages; Competition and land; Japanese; Southern California
  - "Mexican Homes," by G. A. Edsall, California Southland, Pasadena, California (Box-folder 35: 324)
    3 pages; Mexican; Southern California
  - Interview with two Chinese, A and B (Box-folder 35: 325)
    11 pages; Americanization, Race consciousness; Chinese; Southern California
  - "Miss Raushenbush's Investigation of California Yamato Colonies," Tairiku Nippo, Vancouver, British Columbia, 1924 October 29 (Box-folder 35: 326)
    1 page; Communities; Japanese; Northern California
  - "Oriental Versus Mexican Children in School," interview with Miss James, Los Angeles, by William C. Smith (Box-folder 35: 327)
    2 pages; Americanization; Japanese, Chinese, and Mexican; Southern California
  - "Items in the Los Angeles Times in Regard to the Chinese in Los Angeles," by Chloe Holt, 1914 February 15 (Box-folder 35: 328)
    10 pages; Communities; Chinese; Southern California
  - "Efficiency of the Mexican Community in Los Angeles," interview with Wesley Freeman, Assistant Probation Officer, Los Angeles, by William C. Smith, 1924 August 15 (Box-folder 35: 329)
    1 page; Americanization; Mexican; Southern California
  - "Japanese Children in School," by William C. Smith (Box-folder 35: 330)
  - "Japanese and the Schools: Mrs. A. W. Swanson, El Centro, California," by William C. Smith (Box-folder 35: 331)
  - "Interview with A. W. Swanson," El Centro, California, by William C. Smith (Box-folder 35: 332)
    1 page; Race consciousness, Americanization; Japanese and Chinese; Southern California
  - "Intermarriage," interview with A. W. Swanson, El Centro, California, by William C. Smith (Box-folder 35: 333)
    1 page; Intermarriage; Chinese; Southern California
  - Stories, experiences, and opinions: Why California objects to immigration (Box-folder 35: 334)
    4 pages; Goodwill; Japanese; Southern California
  - "Interview with George N---," by William C. Smith, 1924 September 29 (Box-folder 35: 335)
  - Answers to questionnaire concerning the younger generation of Japanese immigrants (Box-folder 35: 336)
    26 pages; Americanization, Race consciousness. Life histories; Japanese; Southern California
  - "Interview with Mrs. Claud Sparks," former visiting teacher, California School, Los Angeles, by Catharine Holt, 1924 December 10 (Box-folder 35: 337)
  - Observations on some Japanese children (Box-folder 35: 338)
  - Life history of Ine Kotow (Box-folder 35: 339)
    4 pages; Life histories, Race consciousness; Japanese; Southern California
  - The life history of a Japanese immigrant (Box-folder 35: 340)
    7 pages; Life histories, Americanization, Race consciousness; Japanese; Southern California
  - Digital copy of Box 36
  - "Odds and Ends," by Chloe Holt, 1925 January, conversation with Mrs. Root, South Pasadena, 1924 December 9 (Box-folder 36: 341)
    4 pages; Competition and land, Goodwill, Population; Japanese; Southern California
  - Reverend E. H. Jones, former missionary to Japan, Los Angeles (Box-folder 36: 342)
    1 page, Race consciousness; Japanese; Southern California
  - Burning of a Japanese flower shop in Hollywood, interview with Miss Spalding, 1924 May 26 (Box-folder 36: 343)
    3 pages; Race consciousness; Japanese; Southern California
  - Interview with E. H. Jones, 1924 May 24 (Box-folder 36: 344)
    2 pages; Americanization, Competition and land; Japanese; Southern California
  - Interview with Mrs. Jones, 1924 May 20 (Box-folder 36: 345)
    1 page; Americanization, Competition and land; Japanese; Southern California
  - Interview with Miss Browning, 1924 May 25 (Box-folder 36: 346)
  - Interview with Mr. Joyce, 1924 May 21 (Box-folder 36: 347)
    1 page; Racial traits, Competition and land; Japanese; Southern California
  - Classified Japanese institutions, Los Angeles, California (Box-folder 36: 348)
    4 pages; Communities; Japanese; Southern California
  - Classified Japanese institutions, Sacramento, California (Box-folder 36: 349)
    2 pages; Communities; Japanese; Northern California
  - Classified Japanese institutions (Japanese American Directory, 1918) (Box-folder 36: 350)
    4 pages; Communities; Japanese; Northern California